♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Okay, I call.
What do you got?
Boom. Full house, jokers
over instruction cards.
I do not enjoy
playing with you.
Everything's so silly.
You guys, you'll
never guess what.
Randy Jackson was just
a big sea turtle
in human clothes,
we heard.
No, we all just booked
a vacation together
to a private resort
in the Bahamas.
Well, that's a lot
of my money,
but I used to have
sex with you,
so that's
the trade-off.
Look, it's not as
expensive as it sounds.
We found a great group rate
on a discount Web site.
Wow, the Bahamas.
I can't wait to get down there
and dip my fingers in the water.
Yeah, it'll be awesome
to nail a hotel masseuse
and then watch Nanny
McPhee in the room.
So, when do we leave?
Oh. Sorry, Glenn.
The deal was
for couples only.
I... I'm afraid
you can't come.
All right, fine.
Since you'll all be gone,
I'll just walk around my yard
naked, pee anywhere I want.
I don't care.
I think it's great
that Peter and Lois
are getting away together.
Yeah, I think Dad's actually
kind of excited about it.
Yes, very. He even bought
some sort of language tapes,
although I don't think
he's using them properly.
I would like
to hear the specials.
I would like to
hear the specials.
Where is the Eiffel Tower?
I would rather
hear the specials.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I shoved an employee at Wendy's
and they called the cops.
You got to warn somebody before
you hand him a square burger.
Thanks again for watching the
kids while we're gone, Daddy.
Yeah, but how come
Babs couldn't come?
Oh, she wanted to be here, but
she got hired to be the stuffy
old woman who slowly comes
around to it in a rap video.
I'm so glad the times
are not changing.
♪ You a bitch and a ho
and a ho and a bitch ♪
My garden party has been ruined.
But I'm beginning
to tap my foot.
All right, I know most of you
haven't traveled with me,
but get ready to see
a lot of airport elevators
you didn't know existed.
Hey, guys. Say, Lois, I-I
know you said this trip
was couples only,
but great news.
We're now
a couple.
Oh. Who's this?
This is Kimmie.
I met her in a pop-up window
on the Internet.
She was in my area.
Hi. Peter Griffin,
all but separated.
Oh, right on.
All right, well,
I suppose I could look into
adding you two
to the reservation.
Yeah, you guys
should definitely come.
Yeah, this
is gonna be awesome.
Relax, Peter.
Geez, I haven't
seen you this excited
since you got that letter
sent by carrier owl.
Oh, my God. Is this my
acceptance to Hogwarts?
No, it's a letter
asking you
to stop throwing rocks
at my nest.
You hit one of my kids,
and now he can't fly right.
Well, fine, then I'll just
throw rocks at the hornets.
He told me to do it.
And thus began
the Thousand Year War
between the avians
and the insects.
It was a brutal war,
it was a bitter war.
And most importantly, it was
a visually spectacular war.
Attack!
Charge!
Sorry, I'm being told this
would be very expensive
to animate, so instead,
here's some stock footage
of an old plane
trying to take off.
They didn't have enough wings.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God, this
place is gorgeous.
Yeah, I can't wait to puke up
a club sandwich in the pool.
Hello, couples.
My name is Noel,
and welcome
to Pleasant Surroundings.
Something about black people
wearing all-white clothes--
it's very peaceful.
We have a special beach barbecue
planned for you tonight,
but in the meantime, please
enjoy all our amenities.
We will. Come on, girls, let's
go wear big floppy sun hats
in the pool and then
be mad when they get wet.
Yeah, I'm gonna hit
the pool soon, myself.
Got to let the lifeguard know
he better keep an eye on me.
I'm here a whole week, pal.
Hey, Brian, check it
out-- HotOrNot.com.
- Ten.
- One.
Ten.
One.
Five.
Hey, I just made
black coffee
in an old tin pan.
Who wants some?
No one? What's wrong
with you people?
Dick Fosbury won
an Olympics on this.
Well, say, this is pretty neat.
I brought you kids an old seed
packet I found in my garage.
I know what you got
your fingers crossed for,
and yes,
they're persimmons.
All right, that's it.
Damn it, I tried two things
that all kids love:
coffee and
old seed packets.
And all any of you
can do is stare
at those Game Boy machines!
I'm sick of it!
In fact, for the rest
of the week, no more screens.
I'm locking those things up.
Wait, you what?
Oh, come on, what the hell?
Aw...
Aw, but what...?!
That's right,
I'm gonna show you kids how to
have fun the old-fashioned way,
like I did when
I was a kid.
But I can't live
without my laptop.
How else am I supposed
to get my degree
from the University
of Phoenix?
Credit card information.
And submit.
And I'm a lawyer.
We find the defendant
guilty of murder.
Sorry.
Oh, hey, you guys.
Uh, Quagmire, I don't think
you can go to dinner
in your swimsuit.
And what the hell
happened to you?
Oh, Kimmie and I
fell asleep on the beach.
Yeah, I think
you better change.
Okay, we'll be down
in a minute.
Welcome, everyone.
I hope you enjoyed
your afternoon,
but now it's time
to get to work.
On the rippin'
and the tearin'?
Even better. We're going
to work on your relationships.
After all,
this isn't just a vacation,
it's a couples
counseling retreat.
Oh, what the hell?!
Sorry, Peter.
We had to trick you guys
or you wouldn't have come.
No. You can't
make me.
I'll get hit with a coconut
so I lose my memory of this.
Aah! I remember
everything!
I was abused
by my dad!
Lois, I can't believe
you tricked us
into coming on a couples
counseling retreat.
I do not like
being lied to.
Me neither.
I mean, wives conspiring
against their husbands.
What's next, huh?
Freakin' Cheney
back in the White House?
Hmm, that didn't link up.
Trust me,
you won't regret this.
I'll see you all in the morning
for our first session.
Sheesh, couples counseling?
This is the worst thing
that's ever happened to anyone.
Wives, huh?
He gets it.
Hey there,
buckaroos!
Who's ready for
some old-timey fun?
I thought we could go down
to the old swimmin' hole
and swim in a hole.
Ugh.
That sounds lame.
Who-whose hole is it?
I'm potentially in.
Grandpa, can I just
have my video games back?
I want to play
Call of Duty.
Oh, I've got the original
Call of Duty right here.
It's called jacks.
Got one!
Will I get two?
Come get in on this.
Wait, this-this game
is cleaning up toys?
Carter, read the room.
They're not into it.
All right,
fair enough.
I just don't want
you kids sitting
around here glued
to your screens.
So let's get the blood pumping
with my Jack LaLanne record.
Bend to the left.
Bend to the right.
Get the big spring.
Stretch the
big spring.
Stop to smoke.
Get a big towel.
Put it behind
your neck.
Tuck it in
your shirt.
Looks like boobs.
Put on a wig.
Dance with a man.
Don't tell your wife.
Take it to your grave.
Okay, good workout.
I got to go call
somebody and hang up.
All right, our first
counseling exercise will be
speaking to each other
with "I feel" statements.
Lois, please begin.
I feel
unappreciated,
like you don't want
to spend time with me.
Okay. I feel a numbness
radiating down my left arm.
I feel like you should help
out more around the house.
I feel like salty and sweet.
You got white chocolate
French fries?
I feel like my cervix hurts.
I feel pride.
Okay, for our next exercise,
let's play
The Oldlywed Game.
Relax,
it's just a questionnaire.
Really?
Whatever, I like
likin' things.
Peter, when
is Lois's birthday?
Uh, let's see, when
is Hitler's birthday?
April 20.
Wow. Okay, Noel.
Yikes.
Joe, what is Bonnie's
favorite food?
Well, she must like
ground glass,
because I keep
finding it in my food.
Cleveland...
Pass.
Quagmire, what color
are Kimmie's eyes?
Shaved.
Sor-sorry, what-what is it?
What's the question?
Okay, last night I did some
personality assessments
based on yesterday's session,
and what I found
was none of
you couples
are compatible with
each other at all.
No, no, no, that's
not a good thing.
But, interestingly,
you have high compatibility
with other people
in this group.
Oh, my God.
That is crazy.
More mac and cheese.
Here, just keep it going.
Keep it going... don't be
afraid of the burned edges.
Just give me the tray.
Wait, so what happened?
Anyway, I'd like
to do an exercise.
Just for the morning,
you'll all be paired
with your
more compatible match.
And hopefully,
you'll bring some lessons back
from that experience
into your marriages.
Okay, so the new
couple pairings
are as follows:
Cleveland and Lois...
Oh, cool! My FICO score
just went up a hundred points.
...Quagmire
and Bonnie,
Joe and Donna,
and Peter
and Kimmie.
Yay! I win
couples counseling!
Look at those
hairless shins.
They're magnificent.
Decades of black
dress socks
have rendered them
smooth and mirror-like.
Grandpa, what are we
even doing out here?
Looking for shapes
in the clouds.
That one looks like the Thompson
Throat Lozenge girl!
See? She's got the boater on
and everything!
I'm bored. Can't we
do something else?
Well, back when
I was your age,
there was nothing better
than knocking on doors
and throwing paper bags
full of flour at people.
That's a thing?
What, flour facin'?
It's the best thing!
We used it to keep Italians
from going to the polls.
Stay home today, Guido!
Yay! Old-fashioned things
are the best!
♪ Every girl wants you ♪
♪ To be her man ♪
♪ But I'll wait, my dear ♪
♪ Till it's my turn ♪
♪ I'm not the kind of girl ♪
♪ Who gives up just like that ♪
♪ Oh, no.. . ♪
♪ The tide is high ♪
♪ But I'm holding on ♪
♪ I'm gonna be your ♪
♪ Number one ♪
♪ Number ♪
♪ One ♪
♪ Num... ♪
So, this is the second vacation
that I've watched
every Jurassic Park.
Peter, you're awesome.
You're so funny.
Hey, Kimmie, I'll pay you
a thousand dollars
for one whole handful
of your butt.
For two handfuls,
I'll give you my car.
All right,
that's enough!
I have had it, Peter!
So, how are the new
pairings working out?
Are you all gaining
lots of insights?
No! I can see now
that coming here
was a huge mistake!
You're hopeless, Peter!
Your feet look old.
This retreat is over!
Fire up the boat--
we're going home!
Mrs. Griffin, please,
I urge you to finish
the program.
No, thank you.
I never should've
come here.
Or at least
not with him.
Is there anything
I can do to change...
Oh, my God!
We're taking this
island back.
Yeah! Kill the whites!
Race war!
(grunts
Run! Everybody run!
What the hell is happening?!
Somebody do something!
Look! We got to get
the attention of that plane!
You got to help us!
Man, those natives
are pissed!
This is like
a full-blown revolution!
Do you think me throwing
full sodas into the garbage
had anything
to do with this?
Quick!
Into the jungle!
What are we gonna do?
Wait a minute-- yesterday,
near the north beach,
I saw a small
landing strip, giggity.
It might be our best chance
to get off, giggity, the island.
Did you really see that,
or was it just an excuse
to say "giggity"?
I don't know, baby--
I'm crazy with the heat.
Take your pants off.
Oh, my God,
this is legit ridic.
I got to post this.
Josh Radnor's
twitter feed is so funny!
That's impossible.
Geez, coming here
was a bad idea.
Like when I brought
museum behavior into my home.
Excuse me, we do ask that
you don't touch anything.
I got to say, Carter,
you've done a good job.
We'd become slaves
to our electronics.
But you know what
we're doing here?
We're reclaiming
our lives.
You're kind of an egghead,
aren't you, Brian?
Vroom! Everyone on this plane
is wearing a suit.
Say, that reminds me.
Everyone,
time to dress for dinner.
Ooh! I want to light
the candles, Pop-Pop!
Oh, boy,
I haven't had this much fun
since I played
with that Bublе wrap.
MICHAEL BUBLE-STYLE SINGER (with
♪ I... just... ♪
♪ Haven't met you yet ♪
Oh, cool!
♪ Your mom thinks of me ♪
♪ When she's doing your dad ♪
What?
♪ Seriously,
I drive older woman nuts ♪
♪ I can make your ♪
♪ Mom and aunt kiss... ♪
This is a very skeevy
packing product.
Oh, my God, this is bad.
I know. If we die,
what's gonna happen
to my mail?
What?
I'm just sayin', how's the post office
supposed to know?
And my DVR!
It'll be full in a week!
I record Ellen every day!
I know I shouldn't,
but whenever she dances,
I'm like, "Go ahead, girl,
it's your world!"
I heard she gay.
Well, it seems like
we're pretty talked out.
Thanks for changing your mind
about drowning me in that river.
Hey. Did you see
those pictures of me
doing ducklips
by a pool?
I don't know,
some island.
Shh!
You rebel scum!
Ah, you're too young.
You don't know.
So, how did you guys
get captured?
Quagmire screams
when he urinates.
How about you?
Cleveland kept stopping
to scratch his back on trees.
Lois don't
do it right.
Come here, baby.
You need them Lee Press-Ons.
Mmm. There it is.
Mmm.
Ah, Peter!
I was so worried
about you.
Lois, when we got captured,
I said, "You rebel scum,"
and Kimmie didn't get it.
That's funny!
From The Star Wars!
Well, just Star Wars.
But I missed you, sweetheart!
Why are you doing this?
Let us go!
Every year we have to deal
with you American tourists!
Stuffing your slob faces,
taking video you'll never watch,
and asking if I'm
the Captain Phillips guy.
I'm not!
Take the couples out,
two by two,
and execute them.
Oh, my God!
Well, at least I ain't going out
with a itchy back.
Oh, no!
This is terrible!
Now, now, maybe
they just shot Donna twice.
Bonnie, quick,
lock my wheels!
We don't have
to make it easy for them!
Scuffin' up those floors
pretty good!
Boy, they're really
going at Donna.
Any last words?
Moist.
Oh, Peter, I'm so sorry
I lied to get you to come here.
I should've been
honest with you.
Please forgive me?
I do, Lois.
I know you were just trying
to do something good for our marriage.
And I'm sorry I've been
such a jerk about it.
I need you, Lois.
I always will.
And if I got to get shot
by ooga-booga people,
I want it to happen
with you.
Oh, Peter.
I love you so much, Lois.
I love you,
too, Peter.
Lois, I think
you should know,
I never cared for your
most recent haircut.
Peter, I've had the same
haircut for 20 years.
We're ready now.
Congratulations,
Griffins-- you did it!
You've successfully
completed the program.
What?!
We just found out, too!
The whole thing was staged.
Noel dying,
the uprising, all of it.
Oh-ho, that's what they
meant on their Web site:
"Staged Revolution
Marital Counseling."
It all makes sense.
Yes, sorry to deceive you all,
but we find that when couples
don't respond
to traditional counseling,
the stress of extreme danger
reminds them of what
matters most in their lives--
their love for each other.
I feel like I
should be mad, but...
I guess you're right.
Lois and I have
never felt closer.
And I did get to kill a guy.
What?!
Thanks for
everything, Noel.
Well, kids,
it's Dyngus Day.
Here are your
pussy willow branches.
Find your sweetie
and give her a tap.
Looks like I found
my sweetie.
Oh, sarsaparilla!
I was going to take sister!
Hey, you little rats.
All right, Lois, let's
just leave our bags here
and wonder where our clothes
are for the next two days.
How was your trip, Father?
We've prepared
a song for you.
Nope.
Ah, boy, it's nice
to be home.
Sure is, Lois.
Now, shush. TV.
Television?
How pathetic.
Yeah.
You know where the
most interesting stuff is, Dad?
The human hat.
We now return
to Police Chases...
No, thank you-- we are
a screen-free family.
...That End in Fire.
That's awesome!
Nobody look at him,
and maybe he'll just leave.
Good job, people.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru